liquidationchannel.com 2018-10-07

# Privacy Policy | Shop LC

### Shop LC. Privacy Policy

The Jewelry Channel, Inc. (USA), doing business as "Shop LC" Internet Privacy Policy is provided to you so that you may be informed as to the practices of our company, which may change from time to time upon publication on this Web site. Therefore, we suggest that you review this Privacy Policy each time you use this site to confirm that you understand and agree to its terms. In the event you have inquiries as to this or other policies, we can be reached through Customer Service at [1 877 899 0078](tel:18778990078) .

* * *

### Personal Information

Your transaction history and the information you provide to us voluntarily on our site is stored in our customer database along with the customer information received from other sources. Some of the information we solicit, such as e-mail address, is voluntary, while much of it is required in order to fulfill your order properly. In addition to fulfilling your orders, we use the information that you provide for purposes such as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping and improving our services.

As is common practice, we may occasionally share your personal information with companies we work with to assist us in providing existing and greater services to our customers.

Our site presently does not store your credit card information, and any of your credit card information that may be stored in other Shop LC systems is protected by firewalls. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

* * *

### E-MAIL POLICY

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail and those who voluntarily include their e-mail addresses when ordering online. We may also collect your e-mail address if you provide it in the process of completing survey information or registering for online contests or sweepstakes. We cannot obtain your e-mail address unless you voluntarily provide it to us, or we obtain it from a service company that has confirmed your willingness to distribute it. Our Web server recognizes the computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, but not the e-mail address, for each visitor to our home page.

Contest registrations may involve sharing your e-mail address with our promotional co-sponsors -- please see the specific contest rules & regulations for details. Additionally, if you submit your e-mail address to Shop LC as part of a transaction originating with one of the companies we do business, the e-mail address may be shared by both Shop LC, and the company we do business with. So therefore please see the specific privacy policy, accessible from the other company's site, for details.

Other than the exceptions noted above, Shop LC will not sell, share or otherwise distribute your e-mail address. Any e-mail address supplied directly to Shop LC with respect to online orders, phone order, and requests for other information will remain in the sole possession of Shop LC.

If you do not want to receive promotional e-mail from Shop LC in the future, please use our unsubscribe form to remove your name from our list, or let us know by contacting us at [1 877 899 0078](tel:18778990078).

If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please contact us at [customerservice@shoplc.com](mailto:customerservice@shopShop%20LC.com) or by calling us at [1 877 899 0078](tel:18778990078) **FREE**.

* * *

### COOKIES

Like most retail web sites, we use "cookies," which are pieces of data given to your browser that allow our site to identify you when you access our site. While some concern has been expressed over the privacy implications of cookies, it is important for you to understand that cookies cannot extract any information about you that you have not already revealed voluntarily. The vast majority of Internet users now appreciate cookies as a convenience feature for shopping online.

* * *

### SITE TRAFFIC DATA

Our computers collect and store certain data from your visits to our Web site. The information we collect from this site traffic helps us to make the site easier to navigate and to improve your experience at [www.shoplc.com](https://www.shoplc.com/) Except for business we work with to improve the sales, services, and experience of our Web site, we do not share or distribute any specific customer site traffic data to any other parties.

If you have any questions regarding any of the elements of our web privacy policy, please call the customer service line posted above. This Web site is owned and operated by The Jewelry Channel, Inc. USA, doing business as "Shop LC".

Our web site may use SessionCam for analysis. SessionCam is a product that has been developed by SessionCam LTD. SessionCam may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, page scrolling and any text keyed into website forms. The information collected does not include bank details or any sensitive personal data. Data collected by SessionCam from Shop LC website is for Shop LC internal use only. The information collected is used to improve our website usability and is stored and used for aggregated and statistical reporting
